COME ON
Come on!
owareru youni
Running like a fugitive,
isoi de iru
being chased by something.
kawai ta mune ga
Inside my heart is pounding,
kari tateru no sa
my throat dry like it's withering.
dare no tame de naku
For no single one,
dare no mono de naku
to none does belong,
ore tachi no ima ga
this time is ours, right now...
itami hodoki kokoro hodoki kage o hodoki
Unraveling the pain, unraveling our hearts, unraveling shadows.
iki o tsunete hashiri nukero yami o saite
Stifling our breath, reaching for beyond, tearing through the dark.
tatakau koto mo aishi au koto mo
In fighting and in love.
owari wa shinai
To the distant light above,
ON THE WAY
yes, we are on the way!
I WANNA ROCKS mune ni ROCKS
I wanna rock... Rockin' my heart...
Is this the first time you
have faced a friend's death?
This is the way of the Shinobi...
I won't forgive you...
I'm going to kill you!
The White Past
The Secret Feelings
There's murder in his eyes!
He looks nothing like he used to!
He's coming!
What?
His Chakra repelled my attack!
Then...
This should do it!
Why?!
It can't be!
Could... Naruto's seal
have been broken...?!
No.
This feeling...
True, the seal is almost off
and the Chakra of the Nine-Tailed
Fox Spirit is escaping, but...
Fortunately, the seal is not
completely broken!
I still have some time!
Do you hear me, Zabuza?
We're both busy people.
I know it's against your style,
but I think it's about time
we stopped playing around.
Why don't we settle this once
and for all with the next move?
Interesting.
What can you possibly
do in this situation?
Kakashi, go ahead.
Show me.
No good...
I can't hold his aura down!
Zabuza-san...
I can't defeat this boy.
I'm...
You... from that time...
Why?
Why stop?
Even though I killed your dear friend,
you can't kill me?
Damn it!
What happened to the
force from moment ago?
You can't defeat me with
that kind of strength.
Wasn't he someone
special to you?
Is there someone special
in your life?
I want to protect someone
special to me.
I want to make that
person's dream a reality...
That's my dream.
Many people misunderstand.
They pity and don't finish off
the enemy they ought to finish.
They let them survive.
To me, that isn't compassion
or anything.
Do you know?
How it feels to
not be needed by anyone?
To live day to day without a dream.
The pain of it all.
What are you saying?
Zabuza-san has no use
for a weak Shinobi.
You took away
my reason for existence.
Why?
Why do you have to
serve a guy like that?
He gets the money from thugs
to do bad things!
Is that No-Brow
the only person special to you?
A long time ago,
I had other people special to me.
They were... my parents.
I was born in the Land of Water,
in a small village heavy with snow.
My parents worked on a small farm.
We were very poor,
but my parents seem to
be satisfied with it.
I was happy then...
They were loving parents.
But...
When I was old enough
to understand things,
something happened.
Something?
What happened?
My blood...
Blood?
Go on!
Tell me what happened.
My father...
He killed my mother.
Then he tried to kill me.
Huh?!
After the experience of
the ceaseless civil war,
people with Kekkei Genkai were
hated and feared in the Land of Water.
Kekkei Genkai?
It's special powers or Jutsu
passed on through certain clans,
from parent to child,
or from grandparent to grandchild.
Because of their special powers,
those of the clans were exploited in
all sorts of battles.
As a result, all Kekkei Genkai
were feared
as harbingers of disaster
and death.
After the war was over,
they decided to hide
their special powers.
If anyone knew of their secret,
only death could be expected.
I'm sure that boy went through
so much suffering as well.
The greater your power,
the more you were feared.
My mother had the Kekkei Genkai.
She kept it secret from my father.
She hoped that for a while...
No, she must have thought that
they could have a simple life forever.
Look, Mommy! Look!
Isn't it fantastic?
Not you, too!
Why? Why him, too?
That hurts, Mommy!
Sorry...
I'm sorry, Haku...
I'm sorry!
However...
Father had discovered our secret.
When I came to...
I had killed my own father.
And that moment,
what I thought of myself was that...
no, that is what I had to think.
And then knew that it was
the most painful thing.
The most... painful thing...?
That I...
that my existence didn't matter
to anyone else in the world.
Same with me.
You told me that...
You'll be the best Ninja in the village,
and make everyone respect you.
If someone comes along and
accepts you for who you are,
no one could be more important
to you than that person.
Even though he knew I was from
a clan with Kekkei Genkai,
Zabuza-san took me in.
My power that everyone hated...
He wanted it, needed it.
Brats like you won't be needed
by anyone and die like dogs.
You have the same eyes
as I do...
Brat...
Do you want...
to be needed by someone?
Are you willing
to give everything for me?
From now on,
your power belongs to me.
Come with me.
I was so happy...
Haku, bad news.
I have to leave the Land of Water
as of tonight.
However, I'll be back in
this land some day.
I will rule over this land.
To do that...
what I need isn't consolation,
encouragement or empty words.
What I really need is...
I already know.
You have nothing to fear.
I am your weapon, Zabuza-san.
Keep me by you as a mere tool
that heeds your every word.
You're a good boy!
I apologize, Zabuza-san.
I wasn't good enough to be
the tool you were looking for.
Naruto-kun!
I want you...
to kill me.
Ninja Art, Summoning,
Earth Style: Fanged Pursuit Jutsu!
Whatever you do won't work!
You have absolutely no idea
where I am now.
However...
I know exactly where you are
and what you're about.
Kakashi...
You are completely
in my hands now.
W-What is that racket?
What... Just what's going on out there?
If you can't use your eyes or ears,
simply use your nose.
That's what happens
when you're closing your eyes
in the midst of fog.
This is the Summoning Jutsu
specialized for pursuit.
I deliberately shed my own blood
to stop your attacks both times
for this.
Your weapons have a thick scent of
my blood on them now.
Those are my adorable Ninja Dogs.
And their sense of smell
is without equal.
You're the one who
was playing into my hands.
The fog has lifted already.
And your future is...
death.
I've had enough of your bluffs!
Don't act tough!
There's nothing you can do
in this situation.
Your death is certain.
Zabuza.
You were too full of yourself.
You're too ambitious
for your own good.
You assassinated the Mizukage,
but failed to pull off a coup.
You left the service with
few men under you,
and became a Rogue Ninja.
Soon after, your name reached
our Hidden Leaf Village.
You needed to raise funds
to strike back.
And you needed to hide from
the Tracking Unit's
pursuit and retaliation.
Isn't that about the reason
why you hired yourself out
to scum like Gato?
Zabuza.
Do you really believe I've managed
to survive with just Sharingan?
Here's something I didn't copy,
a Jutsu of my own...
To enlighten you!
Lightning Blade!
What the...?!
His hand is visibly overflowing
with Chakra!
You are too dangerous.
Tazuna-san, the man you are trying
to assassinate
is the symbol of courage in this land!
The bridge he is building
is the hope of this land!
And your ambitions will sacrifice
countless lives.
That isn't how a Shinobi
is supposed to behave.
Who cares?
I have always fought
for my own ideals.
And that will never ever change!
I'll say it again.
Huh?
Give up.
Your future is...
death!
Please kill me.
What are you hesitating for?
No...
What you said is ridiculous!
You're a weapon?
Just a tool for him?
How can you call him
special to you?
Are you really okay with that?
Is that wrong?
Huh?
Tell me, what is wrong with that?
Well, uh...
It's not...
Zabuza-san counts on me,
even if I'm worthless.
He made me feel needed.
But now, I've lost my usefulness
that affirmed my existence.
Zabuza-san no longer needs me.
That's why,
I am now appealing to you.
Please, make it quick
Cultivate your hunger before you idealize.
Motivate your anger to make them all realize.
Climbing the mountain, never coming down.
Break into the contents, never falling down.
My knee is still shaking, like I was twelve.
Sneaking out of the classroom, by the back door.
A man railed at me twice though, but I didn't care.
Waiting is wasting for people like me.
Don't try to look so wise.
Don't cry 'cause you're so right.
Don't dry with fakes or fears,
'Cause you will hate yourself in the end.
Don't try to look so wise.
Don't cry 'cause you're so right.
Don't dry with fakes or fears,
'Cause you will hate yourself in the end.
Don't try to look so wise.
Don't cry 'cause you're so right.
Don't dry...
W-Why did this happen?
Is this what it means to
be a strong Shinobi?
To protect someone?
Are you okay with that?
Are you really okay with that?
I don't get it.
I can never accept that!
Next episode:
"A Tool Known as a Shinobi."